Four AI video generators, which one is
四款AI视频生成器，哪一款
the best? Kling 3.0 versus Seedance 2.0
最好？  Kling 3.0 对 Seedance 2.0
versus Sora 2 versus Veo 3.1. 20 brutal
对 Sora 2 对 Veo 3.1。  20 个残酷的
prompts without me talking, just pure
提示，没有我的任何解释，只有纯粹的
videos. Let's begin.
视频。 我们开始吧。
&gt;&gt; [screaming]
[尖叫]
&gt;&gt; I told you the code stays with me until
我告诉过你，除非我看到钱，否则代码会一直跟着我
I see the money.
。
&gt;&gt; [clears throat]
[清嗓子]
&gt;&gt; I told you the code stays with me until
我告诉过你，在我看到钱之前，代码会一直跟着我
I see the money.
。
I told you the code it stays with me
我已经把代码告诉过你了，我会一直记着它，
until I see the money.
直到我看到钱为止。
I told you the code stays with me until
我跟你说过，除非
I see the money.
我看到钱，否则代码我会一直保存着。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; I am so sorry.
我很抱歉。
I am so sorry.
我非常抱歉。
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑声]
[crying]
[哭声]
&gt;&gt; I am so sorry.
我很抱歉。
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑声]
[music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Can't let them catch me.
不能让他们抓住我。
&gt;&gt; [panting]
[喘息]
&gt;&gt; Stop!
停！
Get out of the way!
走开!
HE'S HEADING NORTH. STAY ON HIM. STOP
他正往北走。 盯紧他。 停止
RUNNING. COME ON, MOVE! HE'S GOING TO
奔跑。 快点，动起来！ 他要去
THE ALLEY.
巷子里。
DON'T LOSE HIM.
别把他弄丢了。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
[bell]
[铃声]
&gt;&gt; IN IN OF MARVELS, some creatures defy
在奇迹之中，有些生物违背了
all expectations.
所有人的预期。
This is the incredible story of the
这是领航水獭的不可思议的故事
pilot otter.
。
Here we observe a truly remarkable
我们在这里目睹了一件非常奇特的
sight.
事情。   身姿
The sleek river otter, miles from shore,
矫健的河獭，远离海岸数英里，
trusts its
信赖着它。在
Among the river banks of the northern
北方森林的河岸边，
forest lives an animal built for water.
生活着一种为水而生的动物。
But today, this otter is aiming for the
但今天，这只水獭的目标是飞向
skies. Outfitted with goggles and an
天空。 她戴着护目镜和
aviation headset, she pilots a
航空耳机，驾驶着
floatplane with the same assurance she
水上飞机，展现
shows in the current. From glacial
出与在海浪中一样的自信。 从冰川
valleys to wind-swept tundra,
山谷到风吹苔原，
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; So, this is rush hour in Chongqing. And
这就是重庆的交通高峰期。
uh yeah, that's a cat. A really big one.
嗯，是的，那是一只猫。 一个非常大的。
It's stuck between the towers, poor guy.
它被卡在双子塔之间了，真可怜。
Look at those paws. Wait, watch this.
看看这爪子。 等等，看这个。
Bus driver's just going to pet him. Oh,
公交车司机打算摸摸他。 哦，
there goes everyone's hats. Bless you,
大家的帽子都丢了。 上帝保佑你，
big fella. And now he's Yeah, he's
老兄。 现在他……是的，他把
blocking the whole bridge. I GUESS
整座桥都堵住了。 我猜
TARGETS ON OUR LEFT. KEEP THEM BUSY.
左边是塔吉特百货。 让他们忙起来。
I'LL handle the rest. They're pulling
剩下的事情交给我来处理。 他们正在拉开
ahead.
差距。
&gt;&gt; Not for long.
不会太久。
Firing. She's juiced up. Then juice
开火。 她精神抖擞。 然后榨汁
harder. Copy. Let's finish this.
更用力。 复制。 我们结束这件事吧。